Welcome back to my series where I
recreate Ben & Jerry's flavors, but
lower in calories and higher in protein.
This is Peanut Butter World. Let me show
you how to make it. I feel like I
haven't done a chocolate base in so
long, but here it is if you guys don't
remember. One chocolate protein shake,
10 g of cocoa powder, 20 to 25 g of
sweetener, a gram of salt, and a gram of
zantham gum. Mix all that up and throw
it in your freezer for at least 16
hours. Once it's completely frozen, you
can take it out and run it under hot
water for about a minute. and then throw
it in your creamy on the light ice cream
setting. It might come out a little bit
powdery like mine did. So, all you have
to do is scrape down the sides. And then
we're going to go in with our mix-ins
for this recipe. It calls for peanut
butter swirl. So, to make that, we're
melting down some peanut butter flavored
chips with some coconut oil and then
using that as a mixin. And then we're
going to add three Oreo fins with the
cream removed. This brings the calories
down from 35 per Oreo thin to about 20.
And I literally can't tell when the
cream is not in there. So, either add it
or don't. Doesn't really matter. Either
way, it's going to be delicious.